@article{gg2020,
  title={Financial access of unbanked villages in India from 1951 to 2019: A Spatial Approach},
  author={Garg,Sandhya and Gupta, Samarth},
  journal={IEG Working Paper No. 403},
  year={2020},
}

@article{almn2021,
  title={Development research at high geographic resolution: an analysis of night-lights, firms, and poverty in India using the shrug open data platform},
  author={Asher, Sam and Lunt, Tobias and Matsuura, Ryu and Novosad, Paul},
  journal={The World Bank Economic Review},
  volume={35},
  number={4},
  year={2021},
  publisher={Oxford University Press}
}